<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Bioinformatics Flashcard</string>
    <string name="content_categories">Content Categories</string>
    <string name="introduction">Introduction</string>
    <string name="learning_roadmap">Learning Roadmap</string>
    <string name="genomics">Genomics</string>
    <string name="metagenomics">Meta\ngenomics</string>
    <string name="metabolomics">Metabolomics</string>
    <string name="proteomics">Proteomics</string>
    <string name="transcript_nomics">Transcript\nomics</string>
    <string name="epigenetics">Epigenetics</string>
    <string name="learning_materials">Learning\nMaterials</string>
    <string name="content_introduction">Content: Introduction</string>
    <string name="Exercise" />
    <string name="exercise">Exercise</string>
    <string name="exercise_flashcard">Exercise Flashcard</string>
    <string name="what_is_bioinformatics">What is Bioinformatics?</string>
    <string name="text_what_is_bioinfo">Bioinformatics involves computer technology to store and analyze biological data such as DNA/amino acid sequences. \n\nScientists use databases to collect and organize biological information in order to better understand health, diseases, and gain insights. \n\nNow, Bioinformaticians are left to understand and interpret the big amount of data that has been collected by the aid of computers.\n\n(Adams, 2022)</string>
    <string name="next">Next</string>
    <string name="multidisciplinary_field">Multidisciplinary Field</string>
    <string name="multi_field">It is a field where Biology meets Computer Science and Statistics (Nattestad, 2017). Bioinformatics has been used for in silico analysis, which means conducted or produced by computer modeling or computer simulation (Fielden et al., 2002).</string>
    <string name="previous">Previous</string>
    <string name="golden_biotechnology">Golden Biotechnology</string>
    <string name="da_silva">According to Edgar Da Silva (former Director Division of Life Sciences, UNESCO), Bioinformatics is part of Gold biotechnology, where this field uses computer science as a main driving force (DaSilva, 2004).</string>
    <string name="human_genome_project">Human Genome Project</string>
    <string name="text_hgp">The Human Genome Project was an international research project whose objective was to complete mapping and understanding of all the genes of humans (NHGRI, 2022). The project began in 1990 and finished in 2003. Approximately half of the genes identified in this project had no known function, until researchers used bioinformatics to establish their functions, develop gene-based strategies for preventing, diagnosing, and treating disease (NHGRI, 2013).</string>
    <string name="why_bioinformatics">Why Bioinformatics?</string>
    <string name="why_bioinfo">Importance of Bioinformatics (Singh &amp; Kumar, 2021): \n\n- Drug discovery and repurposing \n- Vaccine design \n- Precision medicine \n- Forensic science \n- Genome annotation and analysis \n- Protein structure prediction \n- Omics analysis \n- Etc \n\nOverall, Bioinformatics serves a lot of purpose and benefits to the world.</string>
</resources>